{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785220335","data":{"timestamp":" 946785220335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_tunosi_sovipa_voriza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785227010","data":{"timestamp":" 946785227009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lorewi_veweho_jowoma"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785233654","data":{"timestamp":" 946785233653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_veweho_tuvari_dopufa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785240275","data":{"timestamp":" 946785240275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_sujuye_lununa_veweho"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785246865","data":{"timestamp":" 946785246864"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fihulu_yulefo_jowoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785253521","data":{"timestamp":" 946785253521"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ravojo_lununa_yujaya"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785260156","data":{"timestamp":" 946785260156"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_pazaba_fihulu_rinoke"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785266800","data":{"timestamp":" 946785266800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ponuvi_bodabi_ravojo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785274244","data":{"timestamp":" 946785274244"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ponuvi_bodabi_ravojo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785280875","data":{"timestamp":" 946785280874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hufuvo_jezipi_fekewa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785287533","data":{"timestamp":" 946785287533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785300725","data":{"timestamp":" 946785300724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:nonwrd.6.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785308103","data":{"timestamp":" 946785308103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785312690","data":{"timestamp":" 946785312690"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:lc.nonwrd.len-6.lev4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785320700","data":{"timestamp":" 946785320700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785326302","data":{"timestamp":" 946785326302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::HF.wrd.len-7.rand.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785331412","data":{"timestamp":" 946785331412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785336754","data":{"timestamp":" 946785336754"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 26b9ecc7-98cc-4b9f-81fa-72d3cff47897"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_nonwrd.6.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_fekewa_pumise_vitezu"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785350812","data":{"timestamp":" 946785350811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785351345","data":{"timestamp":" 946785351345"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785351568","data":{"timestamp":" 946785351568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785352252","data":{"timestamp":" 946785352252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785353332","data":{"timestamp":" 946785353331"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785354273","data":{"timestamp":" 946785354272"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785355090","data":{"timestamp":" 946785355090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785355927","data":{"timestamp":" 946785355926"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785358537","data":{"timestamp":" 946785358537"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785360599","data":{"timestamp":" 946785360599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785362804","data":{"timestamp":" 946785362804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785365310","data":{"timestamp":" 946785365309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785367751","data":{"timestamp":" 946785367751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785370462","data":{"timestamp":" 946785370462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785373286","data":{"timestamp":" 946785373286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785377377","data":{"timestamp":" 946785377377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785380582","data":{"timestamp":" 946785380582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785381422","data":{"timestamp":" 946785381421"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785382038","data":{"timestamp":" 946785382038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785385917","data":{"timestamp":" 946785385916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785388595","data":{"timestamp":" 946785388594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785391713","data":{"timestamp":" 946785391712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785393642","data":{"timestamp":" 946785393641"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785394917","data":{"timestamp":" 946785394916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALIWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785395711","data":{"timestamp":" 946785395711"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785396617","data":{"timestamp":" 946785396616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785397105","data":{"timestamp":" 946785397104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785397986","data":{"timestamp":" 946785397986"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785401575","data":{"timestamp":" 946785401575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785404619","data":{"timestamp":" 946785404618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785407044","data":{"timestamp":" 946785407043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785409485","data":{"timestamp":" 946785409484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785411365","data":{"timestamp":" 946785411365"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785413828","data":{"timestamp":" 946785413827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785416496","data":{"timestamp":" 946785416496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785418026","data":{"timestamp":" 946785418026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATAZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785418490","data":{"timestamp":" 946785418489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785419161","data":{"timestamp":" 946785419161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785419371","data":{"timestamp":" 946785419370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785419972","data":{"timestamp":" 946785419971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785423546","data":{"timestamp":" 946785423546"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785426434","data":{"timestamp":" 946785426433"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785428696","data":{"timestamp":" 946785428695"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785431899","data":{"timestamp":" 946785431898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785433618","data":{"timestamp":" 946785433618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785435562","data":{"timestamp":" 946785435562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785438223","data":{"timestamp":" 946785438223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785438693","data":{"timestamp":" 946785438693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785439183","data":{"timestamp":" 946785439183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785440194","data":{"timestamp":" 946785440194"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785441118","data":{"timestamp":" 946785441117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785444458","data":{"timestamp":" 946785444458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785446448","data":{"timestamp":" 946785446448"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785448898","data":{"timestamp":" 946785448898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785451246","data":{"timestamp":" 946785451246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785453493","data":{"timestamp":" 946785453492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785455679","data":{"timestamp":" 946785455678"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785455941","data":{"timestamp":" 946785455940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785456123","data":{"timestamp":" 946785456123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785456776","data":{"timestamp":" 946785456776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785457839","data":{"timestamp":" 946785457839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785458712","data":{"timestamp":" 946785458712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" WAMEUMBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785459035","data":{"timestamp":" 946785459035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785459568","data":{"timestamp":" 946785459568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785462663","data":{"timestamp":" 946785462662"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785462982","data":{"timestamp":" 946785462982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785463473","data":{"timestamp":" 946785463473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785467094","data":{"timestamp":" 946785467094"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785469185","data":{"timestamp":" 946785469185"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785471398","data":{"timestamp":" 946785471398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785473055","data":{"timestamp":" 946785473055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785475492","data":{"timestamp":" 946785475492"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785478010","data":{"timestamp":" 946785478010"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785478675","data":{"timestamp":" 946785478674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785479368","data":{"timestamp":" 946785479368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785480410","data":{"timestamp":" 946785480409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785480891","data":{"timestamp":" 946785480890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785481583","data":{"timestamp":" 946785481583"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785481819","data":{"timestamp":" 946785481819"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785587915","data":{"timestamp":" 946785587914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" c6a1f07b-0951-4bcf-92cd-9a76be2edffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785600432","data":{"timestamp":" 946785600431"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785600973","data":{"timestamp":" 946785600973"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785601201","data":{"timestamp":" 946785601201"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785601895","data":{"timestamp":" 946785601894"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785602972","data":{"timestamp":" 946785602971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785603915","data":{"timestamp":" 946785603914"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785604730","data":{"timestamp":" 946785604729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785605569","data":{"timestamp":" 946785605568"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785613373","data":{"timestamp":" 946785613373"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785625071","data":{"timestamp":" 946785625070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785627882","data":{"timestamp":" 946785627882"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785630565","data":{"timestamp":" 946785630564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785634385","data":{"timestamp":" 946785634385"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785636855","data":{"timestamp":" 946785636854"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785648258","data":{"timestamp":" 946785648257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785659616","data":{"timestamp":" 946785659616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliishi familia yenye furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785662835","data":{"timestamp":" 946785662834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785663668","data":{"timestamp":" 946785663668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785664270","data":{"timestamp":" 946785664270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785670828","data":{"timestamp":" 946785670827"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUGOMBANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785672676","data":{"timestamp":" 946785672676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785675194","data":{"timestamp":" 946785675192"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hawakugombana hata kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785677118","data":{"timestamp":" 946785677117"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785678391","data":{"timestamp":" 946785678390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" WALIWASAIDIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785679187","data":{"timestamp":" 946785679186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" WAZAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785680083","data":{"timestamp":" 946785680083"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785680558","data":{"timestamp":" 946785680557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785681444","data":{"timestamp":" 946785681443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" SHAMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785684566","data":{"timestamp":" 946785684566"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785688138","data":{"timestamp":" 946785688138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIWASAIDIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785692618","data":{"timestamp":" 946785692618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785694891","data":{"timestamp":" 946785694891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785697098","data":{"timestamp":" 946785697098"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785701534","data":{"timestamp":" 946785701533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto waliwasaidia wazazi nyumbani na shambani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAMBANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785704253","data":{"timestamp":" 946785704253"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785705780","data":{"timestamp":" 946785705779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" WALIKATAZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785706251","data":{"timestamp":" 946785706250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785706921","data":{"timestamp":" 946785706921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785707126","data":{"timestamp":" 946785707125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785707719","data":{"timestamp":" 946785707719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785710549","data":{"timestamp":" 946785710549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785714335","data":{"timestamp":" 946785714334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKATAZWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785722530","data":{"timestamp":" 946785722530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785726540","data":{"timestamp":" 946785726540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785729985","data":{"timestamp":" 946785729985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785733019","data":{"timestamp":" 946785733018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini walikatazwa kwenda karibu na moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785735667","data":{"timestamp":" 946785735665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" WALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785736141","data":{"timestamp":" 946785736140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785736631","data":{"timestamp":" 946785736631"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785737631","data":{"timestamp":" 946785737630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785738557","data":{"timestamp":" 946785738556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785742063","data":{"timestamp":" 946785742063"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIFANYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785745305","data":{"timestamp":" 946785745305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785747739","data":{"timestamp":" 946785747739"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785749632","data":{"timestamp":" 946785749632"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785753966","data":{"timestamp":" 946785753966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walifanya kazi zao zote usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785756145","data":{"timestamp":" 946785756145"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785756397","data":{"timestamp":" 946785756397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785756570","data":{"timestamp":" 946785756570"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785757224","data":{"timestamp":" 946785757223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785758287","data":{"timestamp":" 946785758287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785759162","data":{"timestamp":" 946785759161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" WAMEUMBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785759485","data":{"timestamp":" 946785759485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785760018","data":{"timestamp":" 946785760018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785763077","data":{"timestamp":" 946785763077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785765493","data":{"timestamp":" 946785765493"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785767689","data":{"timestamp":" 946785767689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785769856","data":{"timestamp":" 946785769856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785772068","data":{"timestamp":" 946785772068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785774202","data":{"timestamp":" 946785774202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEUMBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785777155","data":{"timestamp":" 946785777155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785779141","data":{"timestamp":" 946785779141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kwa sababu walikuwa wameumbwa kwa nta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785781658","data":{"timestamp":" 946785781658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785782312","data":{"timestamp":" 946785782312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" KIJANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785782995","data":{"timestamp":" 946785782995"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785784035","data":{"timestamp":" 946785784035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785784489","data":{"timestamp":" 946785784488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785785183","data":{"timestamp":" 946785785183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785786159","data":{"timestamp":" 946785786158"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785786401","data":{"timestamp":" 946785786401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785787085","data":{"timestamp":" 946785787085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" MCHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785789868","data":{"timestamp":" 946785789868"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785792204","data":{"timestamp":" 946785792204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785795341","data":{"timestamp":" 946785795341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785798128","data":{"timestamp":" 946785798128"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785799855","data":{"timestamp":" 946785799855"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785802409","data":{"timestamp":" 946785802408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785805658","data":{"timestamp":" 946785805657"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785807479","data":{"timestamp":" 946785807479"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785811029","data":{"timestamp":" 946785811029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kijana mmoja alitamani kwenda nje wakati wa mchana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785813371","data":{"timestamp":" 946785813371"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785813934","data":{"timestamp":" 946785813933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785814892","data":{"timestamp":" 946785814891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785815104","data":{"timestamp":" 946785815104"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785815551","data":{"timestamp":" 946785815550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785815982","data":{"timestamp":" 946785815982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785817331","data":{"timestamp":" 946785817330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" IKAZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785821715","data":{"timestamp":" 946785821715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785823482","data":{"timestamp":" 946785823482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785826430","data":{"timestamp":" 946785826430"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785828667","data":{"timestamp":" 946785828666"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785832747","data":{"timestamp":" 946785832747"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785834513","data":{"timestamp":" 946785834512"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785837077","data":{"timestamp":" 946785837077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tamaa ya kwenda nje ikazidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAZIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785839064","data":{"timestamp":" 946785839064"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" WENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785840108","data":{"timestamp":" 946785840107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWONYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785840865","data":{"timestamp":" 946785840865"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" ASIENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785841662","data":{"timestamp":" 946785841661"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" JUANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785846066","data":{"timestamp":" 946785846065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENZAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785848869","data":{"timestamp":" 946785848869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWONYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785851397","data":{"timestamp":" 946785851397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIENDE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785854689","data":{"timestamp":" 946785854689"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wenzake wakamwonya asiende juani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785856830","data":{"timestamp":" 946785856830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785858213","data":{"timestamp":" 946785858213"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" HAKUSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785861626","data":{"timestamp":" 946785861626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785865406","data":{"timestamp":" 946785865406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hakusikia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUSIKIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785868157","data":{"timestamp":" 946785868155"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ALIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785868417","data":{"timestamp":" 946785868416"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785869015","data":{"timestamp":" 946785869014"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785869461","data":{"timestamp":" 946785869460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785870173","data":{"timestamp":" 946785870172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785870997","data":{"timestamp":" 946785870997"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785874734","data":{"timestamp":" 946785874734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785876351","data":{"timestamp":" 946785876350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785878463","data":{"timestamp":" 946785878463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785881751","data":{"timestamp":" 946785881751"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785883839","data":{"timestamp":" 946785883839"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785885515","data":{"timestamp":" 946785885515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyeyuka kwa sababu joto lilikuwa kali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785887968","data":{"timestamp":" 946785887967"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785888210","data":{"timestamp":" 946785888209"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785888564","data":{"timestamp":" 946785888564"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785890124","data":{"timestamp":" 946785890124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785891334","data":{"timestamp":" 946785891334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" WALIPOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785891777","data":{"timestamp":" 946785891776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785892275","data":{"timestamp":" 946785892274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785893541","data":{"timestamp":" 946785893540"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" AKIYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785897485","data":{"timestamp":" 946785897484"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785899120","data":{"timestamp":" 946785899120"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785901286","data":{"timestamp":" 946785901286"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785903810","data":{"timestamp":" 946785903810"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785906077","data":{"timestamp":" 946785906077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785907873","data":{"timestamp":" 946785907872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785910779","data":{"timestamp":" 946785910779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785913482","data":{"timestamp":" 946785913482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wa nta walihuzunika walipoona kaka yao akiyeyuka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785916113","data":{"timestamp":" 946785916113"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" WAKAPANGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785916517","data":{"timestamp":" 946785916517"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785917252","data":{"timestamp":" 946785917252"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" FULANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785923752","data":{"timestamp":" 946785923752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAPANGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785925474","data":{"timestamp":" 946785925474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785927705","data":{"timestamp":" 946785927705"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakapanga jambo fulani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FULANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785929886","data":{"timestamp":" 946785929886"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" WALICHUKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785930478","data":{"timestamp":" 946785930477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" NTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785931794","data":{"timestamp":" 946785931793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785933271","data":{"timestamp":" 946785933270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" WAKATENGEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785933847","data":{"timestamp":" 946785933847"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785937470","data":{"timestamp":" 946785937470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHUKUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785940601","data":{"timestamp":" 946785940601"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785943073","data":{"timestamp":" 946785943073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOYEYUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785946503","data":{"timestamp":" 946785946502"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATENGEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785948282","data":{"timestamp":" 946785948282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walichukua nta iliyoyeyuka wakatengeza ndege."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785950913","data":{"timestamp":" 946785950913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" WAKAMWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785951446","data":{"timestamp":" 946785951446"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785951898","data":{"timestamp":" 946785951898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785952341","data":{"timestamp":" 946785952341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785952594","data":{"timestamp":" 946785952594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785953207","data":{"timestamp":" 946785953207"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" MLIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785953940","data":{"timestamp":" 946785953940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785958289","data":{"timestamp":" 946785958289"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAMWEKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785960133","data":{"timestamp":" 946785960133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785962696","data":{"timestamp":" 946785962696"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785966904","data":{"timestamp":" 946785966903"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785969085","data":{"timestamp":" 946785969085"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785971762","data":{"timestamp":" 946785971762"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785974987","data":{"timestamp":" 946785974987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakamweka ndege huyo juu ya mlima mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785977141","data":{"timestamp":" 946785977140"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785978530","data":{"timestamp":" 946785978530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785979777","data":{"timestamp":" 946785979776"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785981860","data":{"timestamp":" 946785981860"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" AKAPEPERUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785983068","data":{"timestamp":" 946785983067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" AKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785983419","data":{"timestamp":" 946785983419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785984294","data":{"timestamp":" 946785984294"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785991033","data":{"timestamp":" 946785991032"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946785998508","data":{"timestamp":" 946785998507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIPOCHOMOZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786001863","data":{"timestamp":" 946786001862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786006514","data":{"timestamp":" 946786006514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPEPERUKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786008494","data":{"timestamp":" 946786008494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786010088","data":{"timestamp":" 946786010088"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786013148","data":{"timestamp":" 946786013148"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786015178","data":{"timestamp":" 946786015177"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786015418","data":{"timestamp":" 946786015417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..19.off1.4__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786027589","data":{"timestamp":" 946786027589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 18b83be7-9365-4d27-9145-92bd65a47029"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa furaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786038930","data":{"timestamp":" 946786038928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786039487","data":{"timestamp":" 946786039487"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786040994","data":{"timestamp":" 946786040993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786041911","data":{"timestamp":" 946786041910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786042647","data":{"timestamp":" 946786042646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786043133","data":{"timestamp":" 946786043133"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" MENGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786043940","data":{"timestamp":" 946786043940"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786056467","data":{"timestamp":" 946786056467"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786056470","data":{"timestamp":" 946786056470"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786057958","data":{"timestamp":" 946786057958"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786061573","data":{"timestamp":" 946786061573"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786066489","data":{"timestamp":" 946786066489"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786075008","data":{"timestamp":" 946786075008"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALINUNUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786077738","data":{"timestamp":" 946786077738"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786079957","data":{"timestamp":" 946786079957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MENGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786083062","data":{"timestamp":" 946786083062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja mamangu alinunua matunda mengi sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786085379","data":{"timestamp":" 946786085379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786085592","data":{"timestamp":" 946786085592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786086069","data":{"timestamp":" 946786086069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786086983","data":{"timestamp":" 946786086982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" ZANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786088759","data":{"timestamp":" 946786088759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TULIJIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786089531","data":{"timestamp":" 946786089531"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" LINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786090073","data":{"timestamp":" 946786090073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786091489","data":{"timestamp":" 946786091488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" ANGETUGAWIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786092327","data":{"timestamp":" 946786092326"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786092889","data":{"timestamp":" 946786092889"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786095982","data":{"timestamp":" 946786095981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786104038","data":{"timestamp":" 946786104038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786106044","data":{"timestamp":" 946786106044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786110059","data":{"timestamp":" 946786110059"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786113951","data":{"timestamp":" 946786113951"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIJIULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786115932","data":{"timestamp":" 946786115932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786117834","data":{"timestamp":" 946786117834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786121374","data":{"timestamp":" 946786121374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGETUGAWIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786123565","data":{"timestamp":" 946786123565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786125782","data":{"timestamp":" 946786125782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu zangu tulijiuliza lini mama angetugawia ili tule."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786128511","data":{"timestamp":" 946786128510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786129863","data":{"timestamp":" 946786129862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" KAKANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786131165","data":{"timestamp":" 946786131165"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786132838","data":{"timestamp":" 946786132838"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786136223","data":{"timestamp":" 946786136223"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786138874","data":{"timestamp":" 946786138874"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786141002","data":{"timestamp":" 946786141002"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786143453","data":{"timestamp":" 946786143452"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye kakangu Rahim alijificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFICHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786145674","data":{"timestamp":" 946786145674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" ALIYALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786146495","data":{"timestamp":" 946786146494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786146775","data":{"timestamp":" 946786146774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" YALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786147723","data":{"timestamp":" 946786147723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786148831","data":{"timestamp":" 946786148830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" PEKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786149099","data":{"timestamp":" 946786149099"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786152142","data":{"timestamp":" 946786152141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYALA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786154442","data":{"timestamp":" 946786154441"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786157196","data":{"timestamp":" 946786157195"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786161402","data":{"timestamp":" 946786161402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786164311","data":{"timestamp":" 946786164310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786167315","data":{"timestamp":" 946786167314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliyala matunda yale yote peke yake!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786169717","data":{"timestamp":" 946786169717"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786169966","data":{"timestamp":" 946786169965"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786170458","data":{"timestamp":" 946786170458"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786171183","data":{"timestamp":" 946786171182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786172598","data":{"timestamp":" 946786172597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786174593","data":{"timestamp":" 946786174592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TULILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786176093","data":{"timestamp":" 946786176093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TUKISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786177577","data":{"timestamp":" 946786177577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786177764","data":{"timestamp":" 946786177763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786178887","data":{"timestamp":" 946786178887"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" MTUKUTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786179911","data":{"timestamp":" 946786179911"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786180153","data":{"timestamp":" 946786180153"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786181168","data":{"timestamp":" 946786181167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786184770","data":{"timestamp":" 946786184769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786188734","data":{"timestamp":" 946786188734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786188993","data":{"timestamp":" 946786188993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786191867","data":{"timestamp":" 946786191867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786194110","data":{"timestamp":" 946786194110"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" MCHOYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786195645","data":{"timestamp":" 946786195644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786201701","data":{"timestamp":" 946786201701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786204183","data":{"timestamp":" 946786204183"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULILIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786206022","data":{"timestamp":" 946786206022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKISEMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786208346","data":{"timestamp":" 946786208346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786210990","data":{"timestamp":" 946786210989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786215957","data":{"timestamp":" 946786215957"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTUKUTU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786218409","data":{"timestamp":" 946786218408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786221417","data":{"timestamp":" 946786221417"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786223593","data":{"timestamp":" 946786223592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulipogundua tulilia tukisema Rahim ni mtukutu tena ni mchoyo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHOYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786225901","data":{"timestamp":" 946786225900"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786227645","data":{"timestamp":" 946786227645"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786228979","data":{"timestamp":" 946786228979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786230462","data":{"timestamp":" 946786230461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786231180","data":{"timestamp":" 946786231179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786232700","data":{"timestamp":" 946786232699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786233569","data":{"timestamp":" 946786233569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786235200","data":{"timestamp":" 946786235200"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786236568","data":{"timestamp":" 946786236567"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" YAMELIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786240049","data":{"timestamp":" 946786240049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786242666","data":{"timestamp":" 946786242665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786248901","data":{"timestamp":" 946786248901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786251881","data":{"timestamp":" 946786251881"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOGUNDUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786253681","data":{"timestamp":" 946786253681"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786256170","data":{"timestamp":" 946786256170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786257923","data":{"timestamp":" 946786257923"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786260154","data":{"timestamp":" 946786260154"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786263540","data":{"timestamp":" 946786263539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alikasirika sana alipogundua kwamba matunda yote yalikuwa yameliwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAMELIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786265878","data":{"timestamp":" 946786265878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786266100","data":{"timestamp":" 946786266100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786266563","data":{"timestamp":" 946786266563"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" NDUGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786267304","data":{"timestamp":" 946786267303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786269063","data":{"timestamp":" 946786269062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TULIMWANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786269831","data":{"timestamp":" 946786269830"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786270489","data":{"timestamp":" 946786270488"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786271256","data":{"timestamp":" 946786271256"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786272100","data":{"timestamp":" 946786272100"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" MAKALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786276322","data":{"timestamp":" 946786276321"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786278471","data":{"timestamp":" 946786278471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786283406","data":{"timestamp":" 946786283406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786286909","data":{"timestamp":" 946786286909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786290652","data":{"timestamp":" 946786290651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIMWANGALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786295533","data":{"timestamp":" 946786295533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786297265","data":{"timestamp":" 946786297264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786309115","data":{"timestamp":" 946786309114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786313075","data":{"timestamp":" 946786313075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mimi na ndugu yangu tulimwangalia Rahim kwa macho makali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786315968","data":{"timestamp":" 946786315968"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TULMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786316672","data":{"timestamp":" 946786316671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786317853","data":{"timestamp":" 946786317852"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786319325","data":{"timestamp":" 946786319325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786319971","data":{"timestamp":" 946786319971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786329016","data":{"timestamp":" 946786329016"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULMWULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786331935","data":{"timestamp":" 946786331935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786333909","data":{"timestamp":" 946786333909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786336626","data":{"timestamp":" 946786336626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEMWADHIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786341848","data":{"timestamp":" 946786341848"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tulmwuliza mama ikiwa angemwadhibu Rahim."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786344611","data":{"timestamp":" 946786344610"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786345473","data":{"timestamp":" 946786345473"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786346638","data":{"timestamp":" 946786346637"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786348093","data":{"timestamp":" 946786348093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786348925","data":{"timestamp":" 946786348925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786350867","data":{"timestamp":" 946786350866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786355469","data":{"timestamp":" 946786355469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786357725","data":{"timestamp":" 946786357724"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786360294","data":{"timestamp":" 946786360293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786363303","data":{"timestamp":" 946786363302"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786369138","data":{"timestamp":" 946786369138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786372524","data":{"timestamp":" 946786372524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786384090","data":{"timestamp":" 946786384090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini Rahim alipata adhabu ambayo hatukutarajia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUKUTARAJIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786386602","data":{"timestamp":" 946786386602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786387895","data":{"timestamp":" 946786387895"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786388988","data":{"timestamp":" 946786388987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" KUTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786390251","data":{"timestamp":" 946786390251"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" PAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786390994","data":{"timestamp":" 946786390993"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786408538","data":{"timestamp":" 946786408538"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786410646","data":{"timestamp":" 946786410646"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786422166","data":{"timestamp":" 946786422166"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786425224","data":{"timestamp":" 946786425224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTULIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786434439","data":{"timestamp":" 946786434439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAHALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786437277","data":{"timestamp":" 946786437277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rahim hakuweza kutulia pahali pamoja!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786439629","data":{"timestamp":" 946786439629"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786441182","data":{"timestamp":" 946786441182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786442085","data":{"timestamp":" 946786442084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786442338","data":{"timestamp":" 946786442338"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786443171","data":{"timestamp":" 946786443171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786443304","data":{"timestamp":" 946786443304"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786443987","data":{"timestamp":" 946786443987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786445490","data":{"timestamp":" 946786445490"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" NAUMWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786445803","data":{"timestamp":" 946786445803"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786446506","data":{"timestamp":" 946786446506"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786454440","data":{"timestamp":" 946786454440"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786457990","data":{"timestamp":" 946786457989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOMWUULIZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786463675","data":{"timestamp":" 946786463675"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786491990","data":{"timestamp":" 946786491989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786494680","data":{"timestamp":" 946786494679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786497070","data":{"timestamp":" 946786497070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786499586","data":{"timestamp":" 946786499586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786502934","data":{"timestamp":" 946786502934"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAUMWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786504673","data":{"timestamp":" 946786504673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786506512","data":{"timestamp":" 946786506511"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama alipomwuuliza alijibu kwa sauti ya chini Naumwa na tumbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786509148","data":{"timestamp":" 946786509147"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" SOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786510051","data":{"timestamp":" 946786510050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TULIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786510737","data":{"timestamp":" 946786510737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786511771","data":{"timestamp":" 946786511770"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786512579","data":{"timestamp":" 946786512577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786513342","data":{"timestamp":" 946786513341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" ADHABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786514272","data":{"timestamp":" 946786514271"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" MBAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786515387","data":{"timestamp":" 946786515387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" KULIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786515852","data":{"timestamp":" 946786515851"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786516702","data":{"timestamp":" 946786516701"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786518074","data":{"timestamp":" 946786518073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" ANGECHAPWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786518276","data":{"timestamp":" 946786518275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786518779","data":{"timestamp":" 946786518778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786528532","data":{"timestamp":" 946786528532"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOTE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786534529","data":{"timestamp":" 946786534529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULIONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786553730","data":{"timestamp":" 946786553729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786558037","data":{"timestamp":" 946786558037"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786562268","data":{"timestamp":" 946786562268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786567238","data":{"timestamp":" 946786567238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ADHABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786571361","data":{"timestamp":" 946786571361"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAYA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786582245","data":{"timestamp":" 946786582245"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786589897","data":{"timestamp":" 946786589897"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786598374","data":{"timestamp":" 946786598374"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786627680","data":{"timestamp":" 946786627679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGECHAPWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786630188","data":{"timestamp":" 946786630188"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786632409","data":{"timestamp":" 946786632408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sote tuliona kwamba hiyo ilikuwa adhabu mbaya kuliko kama Rahim angechapwa na mama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786635249","data":{"timestamp":" 946786635249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786636618","data":{"timestamp":" 946786636618"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPOPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786637282","data":{"timestamp":" 946786637281"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" NAFUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786638879","data":{"timestamp":" 946786638877"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" RAHIM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786640176","data":{"timestamp":" 946786640176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" ALITUOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786641410","data":{"timestamp":" 946786641410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" MSAMAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786653817","data":{"timestamp":" 946786653817"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786673262","data":{"timestamp":" 946786673261"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786675931","data":{"timestamp":" 946786675931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAFUU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786677713","data":{"timestamp":" 946786677712"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHIM"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786680987","data":{"timestamp":" 946786680987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITUOMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786683050","data":{"timestamp":" 946786683049"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786685071","data":{"timestamp":" 946786685070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786685230","data":{"timestamp":" 946786685230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_065313"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSAMAHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}